continued our metastatic breast cancer leadership with an increasing share in first line. And we
also sustained our early breast cancer NBRX and TRX leadership with 58% of new patients.
Now from our exclusive N0 and N1, we are up 1.5% in the second quarter.
Now from our exclusive N0 and N1, we are up 1.5% in the second quarter. Now from our exclusive N0 and N1,
we are up 1.5%, and our obese N1 nodal populations. We also continue to grow our total
prescriber base up 16%, and we see future growth continuing to be driven by these exclusive Qiskali
early breast cancer segments. Outside of the US, we were up 49% with continued metastatic
leadership. Our growth was accelerating in our EBC launches. We are now approved in 76 countries
and reimbursed in 42. As you can see in the chart in case study in Germany, we did 79%
EBC, NBRX share. We're having similar performance in other key markets. Overall, we're pleased with
a trajectory for Kaskali and remain confident in our $10 billion peak sales goal.
And moving to slide seven, we're announcing today also updated six-year follow-up data
demonstrating that Kaskali showed clinically meaningful OS in that broadest at-risk EBC
population. That data will be presented at an upcoming Congress. This is the six-year
pre-specified landmark data for IDFS as well as for OS. The IDFS benefit continues over time and
continues to strengthen the case for use in the broadest at-risk EBC population. Safety remained
consistent with the known profile of Kaskali. We believe this data underscores the value of
dual inhibition with Kaskali and endocrine therapies across all subgroups.
So we'll look forward to providing the full details of this data, as I mentioned,
at an upcoming medical Congress. Now moving to slide eight, Kasimta had another strong quarter
up 32%, continuing to increase its share across our key markets. In the U.S., we were up 32%
in quarter two, increasing our TRX share in both B-cell and MS markets. Importantly,
we're growing our NBRX share ahead of our competitors in the first line and first
switch segments, which are our target segments for this medicine. Outside of the U.S., also very
good performance. We're seeing strong growth in Europe, as well as sustained NBRX growth in our
top international markets. We see a continued opportunity in these international markets,